(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Yvonne loved drawing.
She practiced drawing a lot.
She knew how to draw nature.
She could draw people.
She did not know how to draw animals.
She decided it was time to learn.
She looked up instructions online.
She also borrowed books.
She studied the techniques.
She looked at many images.
She decided to practice.
She wanted to start with something easy.
She first attempted a dog.
After several tries, she finally got it.
She traced the outline.
She then colored it.
She was proud of herself.
She decided to take a break.
Tomorrow, she would learn how to draw a
bear.